iceposeidon.com 2019-10-23

# Privacy Policy - Ice Poseidon

At Ice Poseidon, accessible from https://iceposeidon.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Ice Poseidon and how we use it.

## User Information

Like most website operators, Ice Poseidon collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Ice Poseidon's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how IcePoseidon.com visitors use its website. From time to time, Ice Poseidon may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

## Cookies and Web Beacons

Like any other website, Ice Poseidon uses 'cookies'. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors' browser type and/or other information.

## Privacy Policies

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Ice Poseidon, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that Ice Poseidon has no access to or control over these cookies, or IP addresses that are used by third-party advertisers.

## Third Party Privacy Policies

Ice Poseidon's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This Privacy Policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Ice Poseidon. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

## Consent

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Ice Poseidon may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Ice Poseidon's sole discretion. Ice Poseidon encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
